宝贝宝贝睡着了吗
怎么能自己偷偷睡觉呢
说好了
晚上要陪我的
啊宝贝被窝里啊
真暖和
妹夫你又说话不算数了
但没关系啊
我和妹妹来找你了
宝贝真是的
今天喝得醉醺醺的
我连句话都没能跟你说呢
你看看我嘛
再不看我
我就要生气了
你现在当然是在家呀
还是姐姐把你接回来的
你这是睡糊涂了吧
把我们忘了
哼哼我看你是真的醉了还没醒酒
是谁给你灌酒了吗
还是有了什么不开心的事
自己跑出去喝闷酒了
告诉姐姐好不好
姐姐帮你啊
不对
应该是我帮宝贝才对啊
就算喝了酒身上也还是香香的
好想吃掉啊
那可不行哦
姐姐宝贝是我的
只能我来欺负啊
对吧宝贝
是吗
那妹夫之前跟我说的话都是骗人的呀
还说什么要偷偷的让我多亲几口
而且还说了好多让人害羞的话呢
宝贝看看我
你不可以轻易就被姐姐骗走啊
不过你什么时候养成穿睡衣睡觉的习惯啦
宝贝就是嘛
这样热不热啊
我帮你脱掉吧
宝贝的脸热热的
一定是穿太厚了
我和姐姐帮你把扣子解开吧
别动嘛
你刚睡醒
这种事就让我们来吧
姐姐的手会冰到你吗
弟弟身上这么烫
到底是怎么了
姐姐帮你亲亲好不好
♪ You are somewhere flying over water ♪
♪ Rners looking at the world for ♪
♪ What it is ♪
♪ I'm at home and sitting waiting ♪
♪ Watching the birds ♪
♪ Carry little secrets in their weeds ♪
Guess i'm a little lost without you
♪ Living in a black and white ♪
♪ You've been all the color to my daydream ♪
♪ You bring all the quiet to my life ♪
♪ Wish i was the pilot on your space ♪
♪ Shit ♪
♪ Wish it was the two of us in on this light ♪
♪ Wish we had a time ♪
♪ We could name it ♪
♪ Guess something can about you all the time ♪
♪ Got nothing ♪
♪ Everything on my mind by you ♪
♪ Gotthon ♪
♪ My mind by you ♪
♪ I got nothing on my mind by you ♪
♪ I got nothing ♪
♪ But you ♪
♪ You've been gone two million ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm counting the days ♪
It's hard to love myself
♪ When you're not here ♪
♪ Sometimes i look up ♪
♪ And see you float in a haze ♪
♪ But it's always just a light tra happier ♪
Yeah
All of these stars have on me living in my hair
♪ Like a video dream ♪
Coming home is the only me on my own
♪ Going and mad ♪
And maybe it come and methei wish i could face it
I'm feeling so basic
♪ Guess ♪
I'm a little lost without you
♪ Living in a black and white ♪
♪ You bring all the color to my daydreams ♪
♪ You bring all the quiet to my life ♪
♪ Wish i was a pilot on your space ship ♪
♪ Wish it was the two of us in las flight ♪
♪ Wish we had a fight ♪
♪ We can name ♪
♪ It guess i'm thinking about you ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ Gonna fit on my mind by you ♪
♪ Gotta thon my mind ♪
♪ But you i got nothing on my mind by you ♪
♪ Got nothing ♪
♪ But you ♪
♪ Got nothing feel like my holy stars ♪
Foliving in my head
Divirion
♪ My mind ♪
♪ I'm hard as h me on my own ♪
God made me
♪ Like you made me ♪
♪ Got nothing baby ♪